<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: speaking | Lee Brandt's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://leebrandt.github.com/blog/categories/speaking/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://leebrandt.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-03-18T07:57:39-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://leebrandt.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Lee Brandt]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nebraska Code Camp Wrap-up]]></title>
    <link href="http://leebrandt.github.com/blog/2013/03/18/nebraska-code-camp-wrap-up/"/>
    <updated>2013-03-18T07:12:00-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://leebrandt.github.com/blog/2013/03/18/nebraska-code-camp-wrap-up</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This past weekend, I was priviledged to speak at the Third-Annual <a href="http://nebraskacodecamp.com">Nebraska Code Camp</a> in Lincoln, Nebraska.</p>

<p>^<sup>^<sup>^<sup>^<sup>^<sup>^<sup>^<sup>^<sup>^<sup>^<sup>^<sup>^<sup>^<sup>^^</sup></sup></sup></sup></sup></sup></sup></sup></sup></sup></sup></sup></sup></p>

<h2>The Conference</h2>

<p>The conference garnered about 300 attendees from all over the region. There were talks about UX, the cloud, mobile, web and desktop development of all types from some of the regions most talented developers and speakers.</p>

<p>The highlight og the conference was a keynote by <a href="http://www.tedneward.com">Ted "Theodore" Neward</a>. As usual, Ted delivered a keynote that made you think and introspect. Ted talked about "Rethinking 'Enterprise'" in which he asked and (almost) answered what 'Enterprise Software Development' should mean to each of us. I won't spoil the ending. Suffice it to say, I AM rethinking 'Enterprise'.</p>

<p>I also attended Ted's Esoteric Languages session. It was fun and informative. Probably the most I've ever laughed in a code camp session.</p>

<h2>Nightlife</h2>

<p>Regardless what might come to mind when picturing Lincoln, Nebraska, it is a simple, college town. We headed to <a href="http://www.barrysbarandgrill.com">Barry's</a> for the attendee after-party, where there were snacks and beverages.</p>

<p>We then headed to <a href="http://www.jakescigars.com">Jake's Cigars &amp; Spirits</a> for cigars and beer. Being an avid cigar smoker this was definitely the highlight of MY night.</p>

<h2>Overall</h2>

<p>Another excellent year for <a href="http://www.linkedin.com/in/cadambarney">Adam Barney</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/kversaw1">Ken Versaw</a>, the organizers of Nebraska Code Camp. The sessions we excellent and the after-party was epic (as usual). Thanks to all who attended my session and thanks to the <a href="http://nebraskacodecamp.com/Sponsors">sponsors</a> for helping make it another excellent year. Can't wait to submit for next year!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
